<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ScrollView</string>
    <string name="text_heading_view">Pokhara</string>
    <string name="text_description_view">Pokhara is in the northwestern corner of the Pokhara Valley,
        which is a widening of the Seti Gandaki valley that lies in the region (Pahad) of the Himalayas.
        In this region the mountains rise very quickly,[10] and within 30 kilometres (19 miles),
        the elevation rises from 1,000 to 7,500 metres (3,300 to 24,600 feet).
        As a result of this sharp rise in altitude the area of Pokhara has one of the highest precipitation rates
        in the country (3,350 mm/year or 131 inches/year in the valley to 5600 mm/year or 222 inches/year in Lumle).
        Even within the city there is a noticeable difference in rainfall between the south and the north:
        The northern part at the foothills of the mountains experiences a proportionally higher amount of precipitation.
        The Seti Gandaki is the main river flowing through the city.[12] The Seti Gandaki (White Gandaki) and
        its tributaries have created several gorges and canyons in and around Pokhara that give intriguingly long sections
        of terrace features to the city and surrounding areas. These long sections of terraces are interrupted by gorges
        that are hundreds of metres deep.[13] The Seti gorge runs through Pokhara from north to south and then west to east;
        at places these gorges are only a few metres wide. In the north and south, the canyons are wider.
        In the south, the city borders Phewa Tal (4.4 km2) at an elevation of about 827 metres (2,713 feet) above sea level,
        while Lumle at 1,740 metres (5,710 feet) in the north touches the base of the Annapurna mountain range.
        Pokhara, the city of lakes, is the second largest city of Nepal after Kathmandu. Three 8,000-metre (26,000-foot) peaks
        (Dhaulagiri, Annapurna, Manaslu) can be seen from the city. The Machhapuchchhre (Fishtail) with an elevation
        of 6,993 metres (22,943 feet) is the closest to the city.The porous underground of the Pokhara valley favours the formation
        of caves and several caves can be found within city limits.
    </string>
</resources>
