<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Scrolling Text</string>
    <string name="article_title">Environment</string>
    <string name="article_subtitle">Introduction</string>
    <string name="article_text">Natural environment refers all ecological units naturally
        present on earth in form of land, water, air, soil, forest, sunlight, minerals, living organisms, etc.
        <b>All the surrounding of natural things, which are counted as the creator and operator of life on this earth,
            is called as environment.</b> The declining environment has now become a very serious issue for all,
        as the beauty or even existence of environment is in big danger due to some objectionable acts
        of human being on this earth.
    Environment is the visible or non-visible surroundings which support life on this earth. This earth is full of natural surroundings, some are biotic and some are non biotic. Biotic element is that element that has life like human, bird, animal, plants and micro organisms. Whereas abiotic elements are those which have no life like air, sunlight, water, land, soil, minerals, etc. Element comes in categories of biotic and abiotic, further can be divided among four types of sphere like Biosphere, Hydrosphere, lithosphere and atmosphere.

Biotic and abiotic elements reacts with each other in some manner like fresh water, sunlight and soil are used for growing plants same as plants produce oxygen that is highly required by all the living organisms existed on this earth. Human beings use all the available natural resources in different manner for better living on earth.

At its initial stage this earth was so beautiful and full of natural resources that we even cannot describe. But, as time passed, due to increased population the requirement of resources has also been increased and now the current situation is so worst that we cannot surely say that for how much time we would be able to use these resources as they are continuously disappearing from the earth.

Use of natural resources should be carefully planned and executed. It is completely wrong to cut the forest as trees are the key operator of natural cycle. Forest cutting may cause the poor situation of drought, increased heating temperature, unstable seasons, uncertain rainfall, flood, decreased agricultural quality or the worst one “global warming” which is completely not acceptable for the existence of life on earth.

For giving a better and healthy life to our future generations, we all should unite with take some pledge about prevention of our environment with less and safe use of natural resources.
    </string>


</resources>
